yfret.com 2019-01-04

# Privacy Policy - YFret

Thank you for your confidence in our services. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to identify and disclose information which we collect from you through our online services (“services”) that link or otherwise refer to this Privacy Policy.

#### 1\. Information We Collect

Once our customer has identified you as an authorized user of our services, we may request your name, address, email address, and phone number in order to register your YFret account and provide you with login information for our services. Whether you are an authorized user of our services or inquiring about our services, we may also collect your name, address, email address, or phone number when you contact us with a question, comment, or request. Also, if you provide your information to third parties with which we collaborate to provide the services, we may have access to that information. We do not collect any credit card or financial information from you, and we do not share your email address, phone number, name, or address with third parties except as otherwise provided for herein.

#### 2\. Automatic Data Collection

We may, as do most companies that offer online services, automatically collect via cookies or other technology certain technical information from your computer or mobile device when you use our services or interact with us. The information we may collect includes: IP address, operating system, device type, device manufacturer, device identifier, browser type, content viewed, whether you open our electronic communications, and name and location of your ISP, among other information.

#### 3\. How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use the information we collect from you to give you access to our services and support as well as respond to your requests. In addition, we may use the information you provide us for analytical purposes, to improve or troubleshoot our services, and to communicate with you about your account or our services.

#### 4\. Modification of the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to revision from time to time by YFret, and the effective date of the most current Privacy Policy will be stated on our homepage. You can review revisions to this Privacy Policy by regularly checking the homepage of yfret.com. It is your responsibility to remain apprised of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our services shall be deemed consent to the terms of our current Privacy Policy.

#### 5\. Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

We may disclose information about you to our service providers that provide email distribution, technical support, or perform other services for us. We may also provide your Information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process; as necessary to provide you with the services or information you request; when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to protect your rights or the rights of others; to detect, prevent, or respond to potential fraud, intellectual property infringement, violations of our Terms of Use or license with our customer, violations of law, or other misuse of our services; to proceed with the negotiation or completion of a merger, acquisition, sale, or other transfer of all or part of our assets; or subject to your consent.

#### 6\. Your Choices and Security

Once you register an account with us based on the user ID and password we provide, you may change your password and update the information you have provided to us by contacting us via our website or at an email address provided to you. You will not be able to opt-out of receiving certain communications relating to our services unless your account is terminated. We attempt to ensure that your user ID and password are protected via encryption technology. However, we cannot guarantee that your account details will not be intercepted by third parties, and you remain responsible for not sharing your user ID and password with any unauthorized users.

#### **7\. Data Controller and Data Processor (for EU GDPR compliance)**

We process Personal Data both as a Processor and as a Controller, each as defined in the EU Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 (the “Directive”) and the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”):

(a) The Customer which Customer End Users provided Personal Data to, with the assistance of the YFret Service, will be the Controller for Customer End User Data. We will be the Processor.

(b) For Customer Data, we will be the Controller.  For any questions or concerns about data protection, please contact us at support@yfret.com.

For Customers and Customer End Users located in the European Data Region in the European Economic Area (EEA), all processing of Personal Data is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the Directive, and the implementations of the Directive in local legislation. From May 25th, 2018, the processing will take place in accordance with the GDPR.

All data collected through the YFret Service will be stored exclusively in secure hosting facilities provided by Microsoft Azure. YFret has a data processing agreement in place with its p ensuring compliance with the Directive and the GDPR. All hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations. All transfers of data from the EEA is done in accordance with this data processing agreement. If you are a Customer located in the EEA, we exclusively store and process Personal Data in the EEA.

We have adopted reasonable physical, technical and organizational safeguards which substantially mirror the EU safeguards against accidental, unauthorized or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use or processing of data in our possession.

#### 8\. Disputes

We take the privacy of your personal information and any concerns you may have very seriously. Please contact us at [support@yfret.com](mailto:support@yfret.com) if you have questions. If we cannot amicably reach a resolution to your concerns, any legal controversy or legal claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, shall be settled by binding arbitration in accordance with the internal laws of the State of Delaware Any such controversy or claim shall be arbitrated on an individual basis, and shall not be consolidated in any arbitration with any claim or controversy of any other party. The judgment on the arbitration award may be entered into any court having jurisdiction thereof.

#### 8\. Contact Information

Questions, comments or complaints regarding the Company’s data collection and processing practices can be emailed to [support@yfret.com](mailto:support@yfret.com) or mailed to:

YFret, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
3511 Silverside Road Suite#105  
City of Wilmington DE 19810
